邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子
Take your brother outside as fast as you can.
快 迪恩 快跑
Now, Dean. Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
我发过誓我再也不猎魔了
l swore I was done hunting.
我一个人没法完成
l can't do this alone.
不 杰西
No! Jess!
我想他想让我们继续他的工作
I think Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things.
不 我得找出杀杰西卡的凶手
No. I gotta find Jessica's killer.
《邪恶力量》
(大学女生联谊会 东爱荷华大学)
好了 你觉得怎么样
Okay. What do you think?
嗯 太一般了
Um-Oh, God. Too Martha Stewart?
来 穿上这个
Here. Wear this.
我觉得这可能不太合适吧
I don't know if this is really me.
罗依 你不试试怎么知道
Lori, there's a hot chick buried somewhere in there
好吧
Okay, okay.
怎么样
So?
天啊 美女 他绝不会想到你这么美
Damn, girl, he's not gonna know what hit him.
好了 我想他已经到楼下了
Okay. l think he's probably downstairs.
再见
l'll see you later.
不要做出连我没试过的事哦
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
你可没什么没试过的
There's nothing you wouldn't do.
你说对了
It's true.
我以为我们要去派对
I thought we were going to the party.
但我们不能准时到了
Well, we can't arrive on time.
你知道吗 我不觉得这有什么好
If l didn't know any better
我觉得你带我来这心怀不轨
I'd think you brought me here on purpose.
你说什么
What?
我让你不愉快了 是的
l'm offended. Yeah, l'm sure.
干嘛不接电话
You wanna get that?
让它去吧
Definitely not.
不要这样 没事的
No. It's okay.
我是认真的
Hey, I mean it.
那是什么
What was that?
不清楚
l don't know.
是什么
What is that?
- 理查 不要 - 你在这等我
- No. Rich, no. - No, just wait here.
- 什么鬼东西 - 理查 我们走吧
- What the hell? - Rich, let's go.
啊 啊
Ah!
理查
Rich?
Rich.
理查 你在哪里
Rich, where are you?
没事了 没事了
Okay. Okay.
好吧 谢谢你
All right. Thank you for your time.
你的拿铁都在这放冷了 弗朗西斯
Your half-caf double vanilla latte is getting cold over here, Frances.
气死我了
Bite me.
有查到些什么吗
So anything?
我叫他们查了FBI的失踪人口档案
I had them check the FBI's missing-persons data bank.
没有符合我们所描述的约翰·德斯
No John Does fitting Dad's description.
我甚至去查了交通违规
I even ran his plates for traffic violations.
我想说的是 我觉得爸爸不想我们找到他
Sam, l'm telling you, I don't think Dad wants to be found.
看看这个
Check this out.
新的问题出现了 在爱荷华州. -安克尼的克里平原
It's a news item out of Plains Courier, Ankeny, Iowa.
离这里有100公里
It's about 1 00 miles from here.
尸体被发现在被害者自己
"The mutilated body was found near
停靠在9号公路的汽车边
the victim's car parked on Nine-Mile Road."
继续
Keep reading.
官方无法提供
"Authorities are unable to
关于杀手的外貌特征的描述
provide a realistic description of the killer.
唯一的目击证人 姓名保密
The sole eyewitness, whose name has been withheld...
说根本没看见凶手
says the attacker was invisible."
- 这一定很有趣 - 也许什么都没有
- Could be something interesting. - Or nothing.
一个证人什么都没看到 并不代表凶手是个隐型人
A witness who didn't see anything doesn't mean it's the lnvisible Man.
可如果凶手是的呢
But what if it is?
爸爸的话是一定会去查的
Dad would check it out.
- 我们为什么来着 - 被害人住这
- One more time, why are we here? - Victim lived here.
车子不错啊
Nice wheels.
我们是来自俄亥俄州的兄弟互助会的
We're your fraternity brothers. From Ohio.
我们刚路过个镇 想找个住的地方
We're new in town. Transfers. Looking for a place to stay.
你们是谁
Who are you?
你的新室友
We're your new roommates.
帮我个忙 帮我把背也涂上 今天有场大狂欢
Then do me a favor, get my back. Big game today.
他是个艺术家 他还干的真不赖啊
He's the artist. The things he can do with a brush....
那么 莫费
So, Murph..
这是真的吗
is it true?
什么
What?
我们听说上个星期你们中有个被杀了
We heard one of the guys around here got killed last week.
是的
Yeah.
怎么回事
What happened?
他们说是个带刀的精神病
They're saying some psycho with a knife.
或是个路过的流浪汉
Maybe a drifter passing through.
理查 他人很不错
Rich was a good guy.
理查那时和谁一起呢
Rich was with somebody?
还有谁啊
Not just somebody.
当然和罗依·索兰生在一起
Lori Sorenson.
谁是罗依 索兰生
Who's Lori Sorenson?
你背上还差一块没涂
You missed a spot. Just down there in the back.
罗依是新生 她是当地人
Lori's a freshman. She's a local. Super hot.
超级火辣 而且她是神父的女儿
And get this, she's a reverend's daughter.
你知道是哪个教堂 是吧
You wouldn't happen to know which church, would you?
我们的心都和失去那个年轻人 的家人在一起
Our hearts go out to the family of a young man who perished.
我也为之祈祷
And my personal prayers of thanks go out as well...
因为我相信他是为了保护我的女儿而死
because I believe he died trying to protect my daughter.
时间会慢慢扶平我们的创伤
And now, as time heals all our wounds...
我们应该反思这个悲剧
we should reflect on what this tragedy means...
无论在教堂
to us as a church...
在社区
as a community...
还是在我们家里
and as a family.
失去这个年轻人绝对是个悲剧
The loss of a young person is particularly tragic.
生命的失去是最可悲的经历
A life unlived is the saddest of passings.
所以让我们祈祷为了和平
So please, let us pray. For peace...
为了指引和保护我们孩子的力量
for guidance and for the power to protect our children.
我不行 那是星期天晚上
l can't. lt's Sunday night.
只有我们女孩
It's just us girls.
我们会喝点酒 看看
We're gonna do tequila shots and watch Reality Bites.
我爸每个星期天都做晚饭的
My dad makes dinner every Sunday night.
来吧 罗依
Come on, Lori.
我知道你很难过 但你是有权利享受乐趣
I know this has been hard...but you are allowed to have fun.
我试试看
l'll try.
好
Okay.
你最行
You better.
你是罗依吗
Are you Lori?
是的 我叫萨姆
Yeah.My name is Sam.
- 这是我哥迪恩 - 你好
- This is my brother, Dean. - Hi.
我们刚转到这所大学
We just transferred to the university.
我在学校里见过你
I saw you inside.
我们不想打扰你
We don't wanna bother you.
但我们听说发生了些事
We just heard about what happened.
我们只想说我们也很难过
We wanted to say how sorry we were.
我能理解你现在的感受
l know what you're going through.
我以前也亲眼目睹其他人死去
I saw someone get hurt once.
那是让你毕生难忘的事
It's something you don't forget.
爸爸 这是 萨姆和迪恩
Dad, this is Sam and Dean.
他们是新生
They're new students.
很荣幸见到你 先生
It's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
我必须说那是场让人感动的布道
l must say, that was an inspiring sermon.
谢谢
Thank you very much.
很高兴发现年轻人 也来接受主的训诲
It's so nice to find young people who are open to the Lord's message.
实际上我们对镇子还不熟悉
Listen, we're new in town, actually...
我们在找…
and we're looking for a church group.
告诉我罗依 警察是怎么说的
Tell me, Lori, what are the police saying?
他们也没什么线索
Well, they don't have a lot to go on.
我觉得他们因此归罪于我
I think they blame me for that.
你是指
What do you mean?
我说的故事
My story.
我吓坏了 我猜我是看到些东西
I was so scared, I guess I was seeing things.
这并不意味着那就不是事实
That doesn't mean it wasn't real.
你相信她吗
So you believe her?
是的
l do.
我也觉得她很漂亮
Yeah, I think she's hot too.
不 伙计 看她的眼神不会有错
No, man, there's something in her eyes.
她听到了车顶被刮擦的声音
And listen to this, she heard scratching on the roof.
然后发现了鲜血淋淋的尸体 就挂在车上面
Found the bloody body suspended upside down over the car.
挂着的尸体 这听着象
Bloody body suspended, sounds like
是的 我知道 钩子人的传说
I know. The Hook Man Legend.
这可是最有名的传说
It's famous.
你不会以为我们在对付钩子人吧
You don't think we're dealing with the Hook Man?
每个传说都有源头
Every urban legend has a source.
一个它最先开始的地点
A place where it all began.
那关于刮痕和刺破的轮胎呢
What about the phantom scratches
那隐形杀手又什么解释呢
, tire punctures and the invisible killer?
也许这个胡克根本就不是人类 只是个灵魂
Maybe the Hook Man isn't a man at all. What if it's some kind of spirit?
给你
Here you go.
从1851年起的拘捕记录
Arrest records going back to 1 851 .
谢谢
Thanks. .
不客气
Okay
这就是你度过4年快乐生活的方式
So this is how you spent four good years of your life, huh?
欢迎来到高等教育
Welcome to higher education.
嘿 看看这个
Hey, check this out.
1862年一个传教士叫雅各布·卡恩 因为谋杀而被捕
1 862, a preacher named Jacob Carnes was arrested for murder.
他非常恼火镇上的红灯区
He was so angry over the red-light district in town...
那一晚他杀了13个妓女
that one night he killed 1 3 prostitutes.
一些死者是在他们的床上被发现
"Some of the deceased were found in their beds...
鲜血染红了床单 另外一些尸体
sheets soaked with blood, others suspended upside down from trees...
被悬挂在树枝上作为对罪孽的警告
as a warning against sins of the flesh."
看看这个凶器
Get this. The murder weapon?
看起来这个传教士在一场事故中失去了他的手
The preacher lost his hand in an accident.
换上了个银钩子
Had it replaced with a silver hook.
看看这些是在那发生的
Look where all this happened.
9号公路
Nine-Mile Road.
在那个男孩被杀的同一地点
Where the frat boy was killed.
干得不错 威克曼博士
Nice job, Dr. Venkman.
让我们去查查看
Let's check it out.
我知道这是自妈妈死去后 你真正的第一次一个人住
I know this is your first time really living alone since Mom died.
我不是这个意思 但我担心你
That's not it. I worry about you.
在那里有22个女孩 绝对安全
There are 22 girls in there. I'm perfectly safe
那就是我所担心的
That's what l worry about.
你以为我不知道你们会做些什么吗
You don't think l know what goes on?
爸爸 我们不要再为此而争吵
Do we have to have this argument again?
我已经18岁了 我可以独立了
I'm over 1 8. l can live my own life.
那就意味着可以和你的室友派对
Which means drinking, partying with that roommate of yours.
我是成年人了 我能照顾自己 晚安
I'm an adult. I can take care of myself. Good night.
罗依 罗依 别走 罗依
Lori. Lori. Come Lori.
泰勒 你还醒着吗
Taylor, you awake?
给你
Here you go.
如果它是个灵魂的话 霰弹枪可没什么用
If it is a spirit, buckshot won't do much good.
是的 用盐块
Yeah. Rock salt.
- 盐倒是对鬼魂有震慑力 - 是的
- Salt being a spirit deterrent. - Yeah.
但那杀不了它 但可以让他减速
It won't kill him, but it'll slow him down.
这不错
That's pretty good.
这你和爸爸想到的吗
You and Dad think of this? l told you...
我告诉你 大学生不一定就是天才
you don't have to be a college graduate to be a genius.
在那里 在那里
Over there. Over there.
立即放下枪
Put the gun down now! Now!
把手举到头上
Put your hands behind your heads.
等等 等等 好的 好的
Wait, WaitOkay, okay!
跪下 快点 按我说的做
Get down on your knees. Come on, do it.
跪下
On your knees.
现在趴下 快点
Now get down on your bellies. Come on, do it!
他拿着枪
He had the gun.
天啊
Oh, my God. Ah!
我救了你条小命
Saved your ass.
伙计 好不容易把治安摆平了
Talked the sheriff down to a fine. Dude, l'm Matlock.
你怎么说的
But how?
告诉他你是个傻蛋
Told him you were a pledge
被我们耍了
and we were hazing you.
那怎么解释霰弹枪
What about the shotgun?
我说你在抓鬼
l said that you were hunting ghosts...
鬼魂会被盐块克制
and that spirits were repelled by rock salt.
这种恶作剧司空见惯
Typical Hell Week prank.
他就这样信了你
And he believed you?
是啊 你的确看上去比较傻
Well, you look like a dumb-ass pledge.
我只想把她带回家
I just want to take her home.
我能理解 神父
I understand, Reverend.
但罗依现在和两起凶杀案有关
But Lori's now connected to two murders
我不能视而不见
and I can't ignore that.
听我说
Listen to me.
要么你就马上逮捕她 要么就让我带她回家
Arrest her now...or let me take her home.
- 一定要让她询问时随叫随到 - 谢谢你
- Make sure she's available for questions. - Thank you.
亲爱的 你最好跟我回家
Sweetheart, you're ready to go home.
没事了 我们走
Okay? Here we go.
为什么那个钩子人会来这
Why would the Hook Man come here
这里离9号公路很远哦
so far from Nine-Mile Road?
也许他不是总守侯在他的犯罪地点
Maybe he's not haunting the scene of his crime.
也许这和其它的事情有关
Maybe it's about something else.
兄弟 大学女生哦
Dude, sorority girls.
看来我们可以一睹春光
Think we'll see a naked pillow fight?
- 对不起 - 安静点 好吗
- sorry - Hey. Be quiet.
我安静点 你才安静点
Me be quiet? You be quiet.
你不开灯是因为你不开心吗
"Aren't you glad you didn't turn on the light?"
这和传说中一模一样
That's right out of the legend.
是的 这肯定是钩子人
Yeah, that's classic Hook Man, all right.
也绝对是个灵魂
And it's definitely a spirit.
我从没闻到过这么强烈臭氧的味道
Yeah.I've never smelled ozone this strong before.
嘿 看这里
Hey, come here.
你不觉得这有点眼熟吗
Does that look familiar to you?
同样的符号
It's the same symbol.
应该就是雅各布·卡恩的鬼魂了
Seems like it is the spirit of Jacob Carnes.
我们去找到这个家伙的坟墓
Well, let's find the dude's grave
在他尸体上撒盐并烧掉它 把它结果掉
salt and burn the bones, and put him down.
死刑执行后 雅各布·卡恩被埋在
"After execution, Jacob Carnes
北边的破旧的墓园中的一个无名墓碑下面
was laid to rest in Old North Cemetery......in an unmarked grave."
不错
Super.
至少我们知道他是雅各布·卡恩
Okay, so we know it's Jacob Carnes...
但我们还不清楚他的下个目标
but we still don't know where he'll manifest next
和动机
or why.
我也在想为什么
I'll take a wild guess about why.
我想你的朋友罗依一定和这有联系
I think your little friend Lori has something to do with this.
看来你一直瞒着我 这样的大学生活太爽了
Man, you've been holding out on me. This college thing is awesome.
我的大学生活可不是这样的
This wasn't really my experience.
让我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.
图书馆 自习 成绩优秀
Library, studying, straight A's.
太悲惨了吧
What a geek.
好吧 你查清楚了吗
All right, did you do your homework?
是的 我一直弄不明白 为什么钩子人老是缠着罗依
Yeah. lt was bugging me, right? How is the Hook Man tied up with Lori?
但我想我查到了些什么
So l think l came up with something.
1932 年牧师因为谋杀而被捕
"1 932, Clergyman Arrested for Murder."
1967年神学院的学生在嬉皮士派对上闹事
"1 967, Seminarian Held in Hippie Rampage."
这里有关联的
A pattern. ln both cases,
这两起案件中嫌疑人都是宗教人士
the suspect was a man of religion...
都是公然的反对道德败坏
who preached against immorality and found
然后发现自己渴望杀戮
himself wanted for killings...
他说是受一股看不见的力量的控制
he claimed were the work of an invisible force.
做案的时候 看看这个
Killings carried out, get this,
使用的都是锋利的器械
with a sharp instrument.
那和罗依有什么关系
What's the connection to Lori?
宗教人士 公然的反对道德败坏
A man of religion......who openly preaches against immorality?
也许这次不是为了拯救整个城镇
Except maybe this time instead of saving the whole town...
索兰生神父
Reverend Sorenson.
你认为是他召唤了灵魂
You think he's summoning the spirit?
也许
Maybe.
你清楚一个鬼魂怎么附着在 人身上而不是某个地点吗
Or you know how a poltergeist can haunt a person instead of a place?
是的 鬼魂潜伏在 牧师压抑的情绪中
The spirit latches on to the reverend's
并依靠它而生存
repressed emotions, feeds off them.
而牧师自己根本不知道这些
Without the reverend ever even knowing it.
那你今天晚上应该看着罗依
Either way, you should keep an eye on Lori tonight.
那你呢
What about you?
我去看看能不能找到那个无名坟墓
I'm gonna go see if l can find that unmarked grave.
看到快到了
Here we go.
就是这个
That's it.
下次该换我去监视美女
Next time...l get to watch the cute girl's house.
你好 传教士
Hello, preacher.
我从楼上看到你了
I saw you from upstairs.
你在这里干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
我在来这随便看看
Keeping an eye on the place.
- 我有点担心 - 担心我吗
- l was worried. - About me?
是的 对不起
Yeah. Sorry.
这很让我感动
Oh, it's cool.
我和警察通过电话了
I already called the cops.
老实说 我觉得你很关心我
No, seriously. l think you're sweet.
其实你可以尽可能离我远远的
Which is probably why you should run away from me as fast as you can.
你为什么那么说
Why would you say that?
我好像被诅咒了或是什么的
It's like l'm cursed or something.
在我身边的人一个接一个的死去
People around me keep dying.
我觉得我能理解你的感受
I think I know how you feel.
永别了 传教士
Goodbye, preacher.
没有人再和我说话
No one will talk to me anymore.
除了你
Except you.
州长认为我是重要嫌疑人
The sheriff thinks l'm a suspect.
你知道我爸爸怎么说吗
And you know what my dad will say?
祈祷 心存信仰
"Pray. Have faith."
他知道什么叫信仰
What does he know about faith?
我刚听到你们在争吵
I heard you guys fighting before.
他和一个女人有染 一个接了婚的女人
He's seeing a woman.A married woman.
我刚知道
l just found out.
她和她的丈夫一起来教堂
She comes to our church with her husband.
我都认识她的孩子
l know her kids.
而他却和我说什么信仰 什么道德
And he talks to me about religion? About morality?
根本不是那么回事
It's like, on one hand, you know,
我只是想做的让自己开心的事
just do what you want and be happy.
但他却教育我
But he taught me
一直教导我 如果你作错了事
raised me to believe...that if you do something wrong
你会受到惩罚
you will get punished.
我也不知道该怎么去想这一切
I just don't know what to think anymore.
萨姆
Sam?
罗依 我不能这样
Lori, I can't.
你心里还有其它人吗
That someone you lost?
对不起
I'm sorry.
罗依 进来下好吗
Lori.Come inside. Please.
我想进来时自然会进来的
I'll come in when l'm ready.
不 不 求你
No! No, please!
不要
Please! No!
不 不
No! No, no!
爸爸
Dad! Dad!
没事 没事了 没事了
Okay. Okay, Dad, it's okay. It's okay.
我们正在聊天
We were just talking.
然后罗依的爸爸走了出来
Then Lori's dad came out...
然后他就出现了
and then he appeared.
一个子高大携带凶器的男人 带某种钩子
A big man. Carrying a weapon, some kind of a hook.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
以前看到过他吗
You ever see him before?
没有 长官
No, sir.
孩子 好像每次出事都有你的份
Son, seems every time l turn around, I'm seeing you.
我建议你最好远离别管这事
l suggest you try to stay out of trouble.
是的 长官
Hold on there, son.Yes, sir.
没事的 我和他一起的 我是他哥哥
lt's all right. I'm with him.That's my brother. That's brothers
嘿 弟弟
Hey, brother.
让他过来
Let him through.
谢谢
Thanks.
过去吧
Go ahead.
- 你还好吧 - 是的
- You okay? - Yeah.
究竟发生了什么
What the hell happened?
钩子人
Hook Man.
你看到他了吗
You saw him?
是的 你为什么不烧掉他的尸骨
Damn right.Why didn't you torch the bones?
我已经做了
What? l did.
你确定是雅各布·卡恩的灵魂吗
You sure it's the spirit of Jacob Carnes?
没错 看上去就是他
Sure as hell looked like him.
而且我觉得有点不对劲
That's not all.
我觉得灵魂不是附身在神父身上
l don't think it's latching on to the reverend.
是的 这个家伙不会让钩子人来杀他自己
Well, yeah. The guy wouldn't send the Hook Man after himself.
我想他是附在罗依身上
I think it's latching on to Lori.
昨天晚上她发现她父亲 和一个已婚女人有染
Last night, she found out that her father is having an affair with a woman.
那又怎样
So what?
所以她为此很不高兴
So she's upset about it.
她因为这样的道德败坏而恼怒
She's upset about the immorality of it.
她告诉我 她一直被教导 如果你作错了事
She was raised to believe...
你会受到惩罚
if you do something wrong, you get punished.
所以她很矛盾
Okay, so she's conflicted.
然后传教士卡恩的灵魂 潜伏在她的情绪里
And the spirit of Carnes is latching on to her repressed emotions.
为她来惩罚别人
Maybe he's doing the punishing for her?
没错
Right.
理查玩的有点过火 泰勒想把她带坏
Rich comes on too strong, Taylor tries to make her into a party girl.
而父亲做错了事
Dad has an affair.
记得提醒我 别去惹她
Remind me not to piss this girl off.
但我把他的尸骨烧掉了 还用盐埋了它
But l burned those bones. l buried them in salt.
为什么还不能阻止他
Why didn't that stop him?
你一定是遗漏了什么
You must have missed something.
我把棺材里的东西都烧掉了
No. I burned everything in that coffin.
你找到了那钩子吗
Did you get the hook?
那钩子
The hook?
就是那凶器
It was the murder weapon.
某种意义上它就是他的一部分
And in a way, it was part of him.
所以对于他来讲 钩子是他力量的源泉
So like the bones, the hook is a source of his power.
所以当我们找到了钩子
So if we find the hook...
我们就能阻止钩子人
we stop the Hook Man.
我查到了些东西
Here's something, l think.
爱荷华州监狱的日志
Logbook, lowa State Penitentiary.
雅各布·卡恩被关押在此
"Carnes, Jacob. Personal effects...disposition thereof."
有没有提到那钩子
Does it mention the hook?
在行刑前所有的物品都被收押在
Yeah, maybe. "Upon execution, all earthly items shall be remanded...
监狱犯的祈祷室
to the Prisoner's House of Worship
圣巴拿巴教堂
St. Barnabus Church."
那不就是罗依的爸爸布道的地方吗
lsn't that where Lori's father preaches?
是的
Yeah.
罗依也是住那儿的吧
Where Lori lives?
这就是为什么钩子人 在两百年后还缠上了神父
Maybe that's why he's been haunting reverends
和神父的女儿
and reverends' daughters.
但如果那钩子在教堂或是罗依的家
If the hook were there, don't you think
那为什么没人能看到它
someone might have seen it?
我是指 那染满血迹银把手的钩子
I mean, a blood-stained, silver-handled hook?
看看教堂的记录
Check the church records.
1862 年收到圣巴拿巴教堂的捐赠品
"St. Barnabus, donations, 1 862.
一个银把手的钩子
ilver-handled hook from state penitentiary.
重铸
Reforged."
当州监狱改造后
They melted it down.
他们溶化了它做成了其他东西
Made it into something else.
那好吧 我们不能错过任何机会
alright We can't take any chances.
找到任何银的物品都投入火中
Anything silver goes in the fire.
我同意
I agree.
罗依还在医院
Lori's still at the hospital.
我们得破门而入了
We'll have to break in
好吧 你先选地方
.All right. Take your pick.
我选她家
l'll take the house.
好的
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
别去偷看别人的内衣抽屉
Stay out of her underwear drawer.
我把所有的看上去是银的都拿来了
l got everything that even looked silver.
保险一点比较好
lBetter safe than sorry.
来 快来
Move. Move.
罗依
Lori.
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
怎么啦
What is it?
我想知道这发生的一切 这是为什么
I've been trying to understand what's been happening. Why.
现在我知道了 我在祈祷被宽恕
Now I know, so l'm praying for forgiveness.
宽恕什么
Forgiveness for what?
你还不明白
Don't you see?
是我导致了一切
I'm to blame for all this.
我读了圣经里的复仇天使
I've read in the Bible about avenging angels.
相信我 这家伙
Trust me. This guy,
他不是天使
he's no angel.
我是那么恼怒我的父亲
I was so angry at my father.
甚至有点想他被惩罚
Part of me wanted him punished.
然后他就出现了 惩罚了他
And then he came and he punished him.
那不是你的错
lt's not your fault.
不 是我的错
Yes, it is.
我不知道为什么 但这是我的错
I don't know how, but it is.
我杀了 理查
I killed Rich.
泰勒也是
Taylor too.
现在我几乎杀了我父亲
I nearly killed my father.
罗依
Lori.
我现在明白了
I can see it now.
他们不应该受到惩罚
They didn't deserve to be punished.
我应该受到惩罚
I do.
来吧 我们走
Come on. We gotta go.
走
Go!
快走
Go! Come on!
不
No!
快 起来
Come on. You okay?
萨姆 蹲下
Sam! Drop!
我以为我们把所有的银器都烧了
l thought we got all the silver.
为什么他还在这里
Then why is he still here?
也许我们还差了点什么
Well, maybe we missed something.
罗依 你从那里得到这个项链的
Lori, where did you get that chain?
- 我父亲给我的 - 他从哪里得到的
- My father gave it to me. - Where'd your dad get it?
是教堂的传下来的 他给了我
He said it was a church heirloom.He gave me
- 这是银的吗 - 是的
- ls it silver? - Yes!
萨姆
Sam!
你也看到了他
And you saw him too?
一个带钩子的男人
The man with the hook.
是的 我告诉你了
Yes, I told you. We all saw him.
我们都看到了他
We fought him
我们和他搏斗 然后他就跑了
off and then he ran. And that's all?
这就是事情全部吗
that's all.
没错 就是这样
Yeah, that's all.
听着 你和你弟弟
Listen, you and your brother
哦 别操心了
Oh, don't worry.
我们会离开这里
We're leaving town.
你没事吧
You gonna be okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我现在还不清楚到底发生了什么
I still don't know what happened...
但我知道你救了我
but l do know you saved my life.
也救了我父亲 谢谢你
My father's too.Thank you.
我们要留下来吗
We could stay.